They gave all they had to save all they could
The Zookeeper's Wife is a drama, history, war film directed by Niki Caro.
The account of keepers of the Warsaw Zoo, Jan and Antonina Zabinski, who helped
save hundreds of people and animals during the Nazi invasion.
Antonina Żabińska, played by Jessica Chastain.
Lutz Heck, played by Daniel Brühl.
Jan Żabiński, played by Johan Heldenbergh.
Jerzyk, played by Michael McElhatton.
Ryszard Żabiński (Younger), played by Timothy Radford.
Magda Gross, played by Efrat Dor.
The Zookeeper's Wife is a 2017 war drama film directed by Niki Caro,
based on the 2007 non-fiction book by Diane Ackerman.
The film tells the story of how Jan and Antonina Żabiński rescued hundreds of Polish Jews
from the Germans by hiding them in their Warsaw zoo during World War II.
It stars Jessica Chastain, Johan Heldenbergh,
Daniel Brühl and Michael McElhatton.
The Zookeeper's Wife had its world premiere on 8 March 2017 in Warsaw, Poland, the location of the story,
followed by its US premiere at the Cinequest Film Festival in San Jose, California, on 12 March 2017.
It was released in the United States on 31 March and in
the United Kingdom on 21 April 2017.
The film received mixed reviews from critics, and
grossed $26 million on a $20 million budget.
The film explores themes of nazi, holocaust (shoah), world
war ii, biography, based on true story.
The tone is emotional.